var questions = [
    {
        // question 1 //
        question: "Which one is a data type?",
        choices: ["alerts", "javascript", "strings", "var"],
        answer: "strings"
    },

    {
        // question 2 //
        question: "One of these is not the 3 building blocks of the web...",
        choices: ["python", "css", "javascipt", "html"],
        answer: "python"
    },

    {
        // question 3 //
        question: "The if/else statement is enclosed with _____",
        choices: ["curly braces", "brackets", "quotes", "parantheses"],
        answer: "parantheses"
    },

    {
        // question 4 //
        question: " Which operator means equality?",
        choices: [">", "<", "!=", "==="],
        answer: "==="
    },

    {
        // question 5 //
        question: "The array object is enclosed with ____",
        choices: ["square brackets", "circle brackets", "curly braces", "quotes"]
        answer: "square brackets"
    },

    {
        // question 6 //
        question: "Which operator means less than?",
        choices: ["!<", "<", "!>", ">"],
        answer: "<"

    },

    {
        // question 7 //
        question: "Which scope lets variables be accessible on a internal scale?"
        choices: ["internal scope", "global scope", "nether scope", "local scope"],
        answer: "local scope"
    },

    {
        // question 8 //
        question: "The variable is declared by using ___"
        choices: ["arr", "nav", "vari", "var"],
        answer: "var"
    },

    {
        // question 9 //
        question: "Which scope lets variables be accessible on a universal scale? ",
        choices: ["global scope", "local scope", "nether scope", "world scope"],
        answer: "global scope"
    },

    {
        // question 10 //
        question: "Which of the following function of array obejects sorts all the elements into alphabetical or numerical order? ",
        choices: ["pop()", "push()", "slice()", "sort()"],
        answer: "sort()"
    },


]
